desitara.com 2010-06-11

# Privacy Policy | Desitara

Updated as of Apr 22, 2008

The Connectfilms Media LTD Privacy Policy describes how the company and its subsidiaries treat personal information when you use any Connectfilms Media LTD services, The Desitara and Connectfilms.com privacy policy describes the treatment of personal information when you use any Connectfilms Media LTD services, including all information provided when using the websites www.desitara.com and www.connectfilms.com.

Before you begin using the website please take the time to read through our policies to understand how we treat the information you give us!

If you would like to perform any of the following actions, you will be required to create - a user account:

  * **If you would like to perform any of the following actions, you will be required to create a user account:**
  * Upload a video
  * Post a comment 
  * Watch restricted videos
  * Join a community or a group
  * Create a network of friends

When you create an account, you will have to provide some personal information - including an email address and a password. Your password will protect your account from unauthorised access.

Usage information:

If you submit personally identifiable information to us through our websites, we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality our websites, As you use the various features of the website, some of your activities are recorded, for instance the channels, groups, forums, and favorites you subscribe to, the contacts you communicate with, and the frequency and size of data transfers, as well as information you display or click on (including UI elements, settings, and other information).

If you are logged in, this information would be associated with your account. Clear GIFs (a.k.a. "Web Beacons") may be used in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients.

We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the sites and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends.

Voluntarily Disclosed Information:

We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and , chat areas, within your playback or profile pages, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.

If you are logged in, this information would be associated with your account. Clear GIFs (a.k.a. "Web Beacons") may be used in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients.

Your Choices

What is your information used for?

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the sites, in which case you can still view videos and explore the sites, If you submit personally identifiable information to us through our websites, we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality our websites, as well as provide you a personalized user experience. The privacy notices of those services govern the use of your personal information associated with them.

Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other users when you upload videos or send messages and they will be able to view your profile and contact you. 

Any videos that you submit to the websites may be redistributed on the internet and other media channels and may be viewed by the general public.

We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature which you have the option not to subscribe to.. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major site changes or for customer service purposes).

We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous user usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the site as well to create new features, promotions, improve functionality and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing user preferences and trends.

Cookies, clear gifs, and log file information are used to (a) store information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests. 

N.B: You have the freedom to choose to decline to submit personally identifiable information through the sites, in which case you can still view videos and explore the site, but the site may not be able to provide certain services to you. Some advanced site features may, for authentication purposes, require you to sign up for other services like Checkout or AdSense. The privacy notices of those services govern the use of your personal information associated with them.

Go to top
